* Shop

* Our Mission

* Partnerships

 Search [](https://4ocean.com/)

pounds pulled

* Shop

* Our Mission

* Partnerships

 Search [Log in](https://4ocean.com/account/login) [Cart](https://4ocean.com/cart)

Item added to your cart

Checkout

Continue Shopping

**Privacy Policy**

Last updated: June 29, 2023

At 4ocean, We recognize and respect Your privacy when You use Our Service. This Privacy Policy describes Our Policies and Procedures on the collection, use, and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You. If You have any questions about this Policy, we encourage You to contact us at info@4ocean.com.

When You use Our Service, with the help of Our Third-Party Authorized Agents, We collect information to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Interpretation and Definitions**

**Interpretation**

The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.

**Definitions**

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:

**Account** means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service.

**Business**, for the purpose of the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), refers to the Company as the legal entity that collects Consumers' personal information and determines the purposes and means of the processing of Consumers' personal information, or on behalf of which such information is collected and that alone, or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of consumers' personal information, that does business in the State of California.

**Company** (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Agreement) refers to 4ocean PBC, [3600 FAU BLVD BOCA RATON FL. 33431](https://www.google.com/maps/search/3600+FAU+BLVD+BOCA+RATON+FL.+33431?entry=gmail&source=g).

For the purpose of the GDPR, the Company is the Data Controller.

**Consumer**, for the purpose of the CCPA, means a natural person who is a California resident. A resident, as defined in the law, includes (1) every individual who is in the USA for other than a temporary or transitory purpose, and (2) every individual who is domiciled in the USA who is outside the USA for a temporary or transitory purpose.

For the purposes of the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (VCDPA), a Consumer is “a natural person who is a resident of the Commonwealth acting only in an individual or household content. It does not include a natural person acting in a commercial or employment context.”  

**Cookies** are small files that are placed on Your computer, mobile device or any other device by a website, containing the details of Your browsing history on that website among its many uses.

**Cross-context behavioral advertising**, as defined by the California Privacy Rights Act (CPRA) is “the targeting of advertising to a consumer based on the consumer's personal information obtained from the consumer's activity across businesses, distinctly-branded websites, applications, or services, other than the business, distinctly-branded website, application, or service with which the consumer intentionally interacts.”

**Data Controller**, for the purposes of the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), refers to the Company as the legal person which alone or jointly with others determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data.

For the purposes of the VCDPA, **controller** is defined as “defined as a natural or legal person that, alone or jointly with others, determines the purpose and means of processing personal data, and **processor** is defined as “defined as a natural or legal person that processes personal data on behalf of a controller.” 

**Device** means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone, or a digital tablet.

**Do Not Track** (DNT) is a concept that has been promoted by US regulatory authorities, in particular the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC), for the Internet industry to develop and implement a mechanism for allowing internet users to control the tracking of their online activities across websites.

**Personal Data** is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.

For the purposes for GDPR, Personal Data means any information relating to You such as a name, an identification number, location data, online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural, or social identity.

For the purposes of the CCPA, Personal Data means any information that identifies, relates to, describes or is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with You.

For the purposes of the VCDPA, Personal Data means “any information that is linked or reasonably linkable an identified or identifiable natural person.” Exceptions to this definition include: publicly available information and data which has been de-identified (information that "cannot reasonably be linked to an identified or identifiable natural person \[or\] a device linked to such person").

**Sale**, for the purpose of the CCPA, means selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a Consumer's personal information to another business or a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration.

For the purposes of the VCDPA, “sale” means the exchange of personal data for monetary consideration. 

**Service** refers to the Website.

**Service Provider** means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used. For the purpose of the GDPR, Service Providers are considered Data Processors.

**Targeted Advertising**, for the purposes of the VCDPA, means “displaying advertisements to a consumer where the advertisement is selected based on personal data obtained from that consumer's activities over time and across nonaffiliated websites or online applications to predict such consumer's preferences or interests;” and specifically excludes advertisements based on activities within a controller's own websites or online applications; advertisements based on the context of a consumer's current search query, visit to a website, or online application; advertisements directed to a consumer in response to the consumer's request for information or feedback; and

processing personal data processed solely for measuring or reporting advertising performance, reach, or frequency.

**Third-party Social Media Service** refers to any website or any social network website through which a User can log in or create an account to use the Service.

**Usage Data** refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

**Website** refers to 4ocean, accessible from [www.4ocean.com](https://www.termsfeed.com/live/www.4ocean.com)

**You** means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.

Under GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), You can be referred to as the Data Subject or as the User as you are the individual using the Service.

**Collecting and Using Your Personal Data**

**Information We Collect**

**Information You Provide to Us** 

While using Our Service, We collect personal information you provide to us that can be used to contact. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

Email address

First name and last name

Phone number

Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City

**Information Collected Automatically** 

**Usage Data**

Usage Data is collected automatically when visiting the Website, either from a computer or mobile device.

Usage Data may include information such as Your Device's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browsing history and interactions with our Website, geolocation data, and unique device identifiers. 

This data may be collected using browser cookies and other tracking technologies.

**Information From Other Sources**

We may collect personal information about You from third-party sources, including ad networks and data analytic providers. 

**Retention of Your Personal Data**

We will not retain Your Personal Data for any longer than is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, or as is necessary to comply with governing laws, resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

We will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

**Purpose of Processing Personal Data**

We may use Personal Data for the following purposes:

**To provide and maintain the quality our Service**, including to monitor the usage of our Service.

**To manage Your Account:** to manage Your registration as a user of the Service. The Personal Data You provide can give You access to different functionalities of the Service that are available to You as a registered user.

**For the performance of a contract:** the development, compliance and undertaking of the purchase contract for the products, items, or services You have purchased or of any other contract with Us through the Service.

**To contact You:** To contact You by email, telephone calls, SMS, or other equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile application's push notifications regarding updates or informative communications related to the functionalities, products, or contracted services, including the security updates, when necessary or reasonable for their implementation.

**To provide You** with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services, and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless You have opted not to receive such information.

**To manage Your requests:** To attend and manage Your requests to Us.

**For business transfers:** We may use Your information to evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Data held by Us about our Service users is among the assets transferred.

**For other purposes**: We may use Your information for other purposes, such as advertising and marketing, audit current interactions, internal research, data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Service, products, services, marketing, and your experience.

**How We Disclose Information**

We may share Your personal information in the following situations:

When You sign up for Marketing Emails

When You visit and browse Our Website

When You Purchase Products on Our Website

Information Disclosed for Business or Commercial Purposes in the Last 12 Months and Categories of parties Disclosed To:

**Service Providers:** We may share Your personal information with Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service, for fulfillment of sales and payment processing, conduct customer support, marketing, to contact You.

**For business transfers:** We may share or transfer Your personal information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of Our business to another company.

**With Affiliates:** We may share Your information with Our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include Our parent company and any other subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that We control or that are under common control with Us.

**With business partners:** If the Company is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, Your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before Your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

**As required by law:** under certain circumstances, the Company may be required to disclose Your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

**Other legal requirements**

The Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

Comply with a legal obligation

Protect and defend the rights or property of the Company

Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service

Protect the personal safety of Users of the Service or the public

Protect against legal liability

**With other users:** when You share personal information or otherwise interact in the public areas with other users, such information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside. If You interact with other users or register through a Third-Party Social Media Service, Your contacts on the Third-Party Social Media Service may see Your name, profile, pictures and description of Your activity. Similarly, other users will be able to view descriptions of Your activity, communicate with You and view Your profile.

**With Your consent**: We may disclose Your personal information for any other purpose with Your consent.

**Transfer of Your Personal Data**

Your information, including Personal Data, is processed at the Company's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located. It means that this information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of Your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from Your jurisdiction.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your submission of such information represents Your agreement to that transfer.

The Company will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of Your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of Your data and other personal information.

**Security of Your Personal Data**

The security of Your Personal Data is important to Us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Detailed Information on the Processing of Your Personal Data**

The Service Providers We use may have access to Your Personal Data. These third-party vendors collect, store, use, process, and transfer information about Your activity on Our Service in accordance with their Privacy Policies.

**Analytics**

We may use third-party Service providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

**Email Marketing**

We may use Your Personal Data to contact You with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to You. You may opt-out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from Us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email We send or by contacting Us.

We may use Email Marketing Service Providers to manage and send emails to You.

**Gorgias**

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://replyco.com/privacy-policy/](https://replyco.com/privacy-policy/)

**Payments**

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we may use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect Your payment card details. That information is provided directly to Our third-party payment processors whose use of Your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

**Apple Store In-App Payments**

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/)

**PayPal**

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)

**Tracking Technologies and Cookies**

We use Cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on Our Service and store certain information. Tracking technologies used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze Our Service. The technologies We use may include:

**Cookies or Browser Cookies.** A cookie is a small file placed on Your Device. You can instruct Your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. However, if You do not accept Cookies, You may not be able to use some parts of our Service. Unless you have adjusted Your browser setting so that it will refuse Cookies, our Service may use Cookies.

**Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Service may use local stored objects (or Flash Cookies) to collect and store information about Your preferences or Your activity on our Service. Flash Cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as those used for Browser Cookies. For more information on how You can delete Flash Cookies, please read "Where can I change the settings for disabling, or deleting local shared objects?" available at [https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html#main\_Where\_can\_I\_change\_the\_settings\_for\_disabling\_\_or\_deleting\_local\_shared\_objects\_](https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html#main_Where_can_I_change_the_settings_for_disabling__or_deleting_local_shared_objects_)

**Web Beacons.** Certain sections of our Service and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of a certain section and verifying system and server integrity).

Cookies can be "Persistent" or "Session" Cookies. Persistent Cookies remain on Your personal computer or mobile device when You go offline, while Session Cookies are deleted as soon as You close Your web browser. 

We use both Session and Persistent Cookies for the purposes set out below:

**Necessary / Essential Cookies**

Type: Session Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies are essential to provide You with services available through the Website and to enable You to use some of its features. They help to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts. Without these Cookies, the services that You have asked for cannot be provided, and We only use these Cookies to provide You with those services.

**Cookies Policy / Notice Acceptance Cookies**

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies identify if users have accepted the use of cookies on the Website.

**Functionality Cookies**

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies allow us to remember choices You make when You use the Website, such as remembering your login details or language preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You with a more personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter your preferences every time You use the Website.

**Tracking and Performance Cookies**

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Third-Parties

Purpose: These Cookies are used to track information about traffic to the Website and how users use the Website. The information gathered via these Cookies may directly or indirectly identify you as an individual visitor. This is because the information collected is typically linked to a pseudonymous identifier associated with the device you use to access the Website. We may also use these Cookies to test new pages, features or new functionality of the Website to see how our users react to them.

For more information about the cookies we use and your choices regarding cookies, please visit our Cookies Policy or the Cookies section of our Privacy Policy.

**Canadian Privacy** 

4ocean complies with the Canadian laws known as the Canadian Anti-Spam Law (CASL) and the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA). If the individual consents to providing contact information or consents to receiving electronic information from Us, the individual may receive communications from Us. The communications may include printed or electronic newsletters, email communications, advertising and marketing materials, or social media interactions. At any time, the individual may opt-out of communications from Us by selecting the “unsubscribe” option on any of the electronic communications, and all communications to the individual will cease.

**GDPR Privacy**

This section provides additional information for people in the European Economic Area (EEA) or United Kingdom (UK). The terms used in this section have the same meaning as in the General Data Protection Regulation and the UK Data Protection Act (GDPR). The term “personal information” as used in this notice has the same meaning as “personal data” in the GDPR.

**Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data under GDPR**

We may process Personal Data under the following conditions:

**Consent:** You have given Your consent for processing Personal Data for one or more specific purposes.

**Performance of a contract:** Provision of Personal Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with You and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof.

**Legal obligations:** Processing Personal Data is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Company is subject.

**Vital interests:** Processing Personal Data is necessary in order to protect Your vital interests or of another natural person.

**Public interests:** Processing Personal Data is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Company.

**Legitimate interests:** Processing Personal Data is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Company.

In any case, the Company will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

**International Data**

Transfers

Our website servers are located in the United States, which has not been the subject of an adequacy decision by European data protection authorities. By interacting with this website, you are transmitting your personal data to the United States.

**Your Rights under the GDPR**

The Company undertakes to respect the confidentiality of Your Personal Data and to guarantee You can exercise Your rights.

You have the right under this Privacy Policy, and by law if You are within the EU, to:

**Right to access to Your Personal Data.** The right to access, update or delete the information We have on You. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of Your Personal Data directly within Your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact Us to assist You. This also enables You to receive a copy of the Personal Data We hold about You.

**Right to rectify Personal Data that We hold about You.** You have the right to have any incomplete or inaccurate information We hold about You corrected.

**Object to processing of Your Personal Data.** This right exists where We are relying on a legitimate interest as the legal basis for Our processing and there is something about Your particular situation, which makes You want to object to our processing of Your Personal Data on this ground. You also have the right to object where We are processing Your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes.

**Request erasure of Your Personal Data.** You have the right to ask Us to delete or remove Personal Data when there is no good reason for Us to continue processing it.

**Request the transfer of Your Personal Data.** We will provide to You, or to a third-party You have chosen, Your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Please note that this right only applies to automated information which You initially provided consent for Us to use or where We used the information to perform a contract with You.

**Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.** You have a right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. For more information, you can visit the Information Commissioner’s Office website at https://ico.org.uk/, or see a list of EU Data Protection Authorities at https://www.gdprregister.eu/gdpr/dpa-gdpr/.

**Withdraw Your consent.** You have the right to withdraw Your consent on using your Personal Data. If You withdraw Your consent, We may not be able to provide You with access to certain specific functionalities of the Service.

**Exercising of Your GDPR Data Protection Rights**

You may exercise Your rights of access, rectification, cancellation, and opposition by contacting Us through the submission of a Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com). Please note that we may ask You to verify Your identity before responding to such requests. If You make a request, We will try our best to respond to You as soon as possible.

**California Privacy Rights**

This privacy notice section for California residents pursuant to the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), and expanded by the California Privacy Rights Act (CPRA), and supplements the information contained in Our Privacy Policy and it applies solely to all visitors, users, and others who reside in the State of California. The terms in this section have the same meaning as in the CCPA. This section does not apply to information that is not considered “personal information,” such as anonymous, deidentified, or aggregated information, nor does it apply to publicly available information as defined in the CCPA. 

**Categories of Personal Information Collected**

We may collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular Consumer or Device. The following is a list of categories of personal information which we may collect or may have been collected from California residents within the last twelve (12) months.

Please note that the categories and examples provided in the list below are those defined in the CCPA / CPRA. This does not mean that all examples of that category of personal information were in fact collected by Us, but reflects our good faith belief to the best of our knowledge that some of that information from the applicable category may be and may have been collected. For example, certain categories of personal information would only be collected if You voluntarily provided such personal information directly to Us.

**Category A: Identifiers.**

Examples: A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, driver's license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.

Collected: Yes.

**Category B: Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)).**

Examples: A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver's license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories.

Collected: Yes.

**Category C: Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law.**

Examples: Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information).

Collected: No.

**Category D: Commercial information.**

Examples: Records and history of products or services purchased or considered.

Collected: Yes.

**Category E: Biometric information.**

Examples: Genetic, physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics, or activity patterns used to extract a template or other identifier or identifying information, such as, fingerprints, faceprints, and voiceprints, iris or retina scans, keystroke, gait, or other physical patterns, and sleep, health, or exercise data.

Collected: No.

**Category F: Internet or other similar network activity.**

Examples: Interaction with our Service or advertisement.

Collected: Yes.

**Category G: Geolocation data.**

Examples: Approximate physical location.

Collected: No.

**Category H: Sensory data.**

Examples: Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information.

Collected: No.

**Category I: Professional or employment-related information.**

Examples: Current or past job history or performance evaluations.

Collected: No.

**Category J: Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)).**

Examples: Education records directly related to a student maintained by an educational institution or party acting on its behalf, such as grades, transcripts, class lists, student schedules, student identification codes, student financial information, or student disciplinary records.

Collected: No.

**Category K: Inferences drawn from other personal information.**

Examples: Profile reflecting a person's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.

Collected: No.

**Under CCPA** / **CPRA, personal information does not include**:

Publicly available information from government records

Deidentified or aggregated consumer information

Information excluded from the CCPA's scope, such as:

Health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data

Personal Information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA), and the Driver's Privacy Protection Act of 1994

**Sources of Personal Information**

We obtain the categories of personal information listed above from the following categories of sources:

**Directly from You**. For example, from the forms You voluntarily complete on our Service, preferences You express or provide through our Service, or from Your purchases on our Service.

**Indirectly from You**. For example, from observing Your activity on our Service.

**Automatically from You**. For example, through cookies We or our Service Providers set on Your Device as You navigate through our Service.

**From Service Providers**. For example, third-party vendors to monitor and analyze the use of our Service, third-party vendors for payment processing, or other third-party vendors that We use to provide the Service to You.

**Use of Personal Information for Business Purposes or Commercial Purposes**

We may use or disclose personal information We collect for "business purposes" or "commercial purposes" (as defined under the CCPA / CPRA), which may include the following examples:

To operate our Service and provide You with our Service.

To provide You with support and to respond to Your inquiries, including to investigate and address Your concerns and monitor and improve our Service.

To fulfill or meet the reason You provided the information. For example, if You share Your contact information to ask a question about our Service, We will use that personal information to respond to Your inquiry. If You provide Your personal information to purchase a product or service, We will use that information to process Your payment and facilitate delivery.

To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.

As described to You when collecting Your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the CCPA / CPRA.

For internal administrative and auditing purposes.

To detect security incidents and protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, including, when necessary, to prosecute those responsible for such activities.

Please note that the examples provided above are illustrative and not intended to be exhaustive. For more details on how we use this information, please refer to the "Use of Your Personal Data" section.

If We decide to collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information We collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes We will update this Privacy Policy.

**Disclosure of Personal Information for Business Purposes or Commercial Purposes**

We may use or disclose and may have used or disclosed in the last twelve (12) months the following categories of personal information for business or commercial purposes:

Category A: Identifiers

Category B: Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))

Category D: Commercial information

Category F: Internet or other similar network activity

When We disclose personal information for a business purpose or a commercial purpose, We enter a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose except performing the contract.

**Disclosure of Personal Information** **Advertising**

We share limited information to help ensure You receive more useful and relevant ads and to measure their effectiveness. Any personal information We may have shared for the purpose of cross-context behavioral advertising, as that term is defined by the California Privacy Rights Act, in the twelve months prior to the effective date of this Disclosure falls into the following categories: 

Identifiers such as a cookie, a device identifier, or a code derived from applying irreversible cryptography to other information like an email address; We never share your name or other information that directly identifies You.

Internet or other electronic network activity information

Please note that the categories listed above are those defined in the CCPA/ CPRA. This does not mean that all examples of that category of personal information were in fact disclosed, but reflects our good faith belief to the best of our knowledge that some of that information from the applicable category may be and may have been disclosed.

**Sharing or Sale of Personal Information**

As defined in the CCPA, "sell" and "sale" mean selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a consumer's personal information by the business to a third party for valuable consideration. This means that We may have received some kind of benefit in return for sharing personal information, but not necessarily a monetary benefit.

Please note that the categories listed below are those defined in the CCPA. This does not mean that all examples of that category of personal information were in fact sold, but reflects our good faith belief to the best of our knowledge that some of that information from the applicable category may be and may have been shared for value in return.

We may share and may have shared in the last twelve (12) months the following categories of personal information:

Category A: Identifiers

Category B: Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))

Category D: Commercial information

Category F: Internet or other similar network activity

We may share Your personal information identified in the above categories with the following categories of third parties:

Service Providers

Payment processors

Our affiliates

Our business partners

Third party vendors to whom You or Your agents authorize Us to disclose Your personal information in connection with products or services We provide to You

You may opt-out of these data practices HERE (insert link)

We do not knowingly collect personal information from minors under the age of 16 through our Service. We do not knowingly sell or share the personal information of Consumers less than 16 years of age, unless We receive affirmative authorization (the "right to opt-in") from either the Consumer who is between 13 and 16 years of age, or the parent or guardian of a Consumer less than 13 years of age. Consumers who opt-in to the sale of personal information may opt-out of future sales at any time. To exercise the right to opt-out, You (or Your authorized representative) may submit a request to Us by contacting Us at the link above.

If You have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 (or 16) has provided Us with personal information, please contact Us with sufficient detail to enable Us to delete that information.

**Your Rights under the CCPA / CPRA**

The CCPA provides California residents with specific rights regarding their personal information. If You are a resident of California, You have the following rights: A Request to Know, Request to Correct, or a Request to Delete by submitting a Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com). 

**The right to request access.** You have the right to be know and request access to information we have collected on You in the past 12 months. Once We receive and confirm Your request, We will disclose to You:

The categories of personal information We collected about You

The categories of sources for the personal information We collected about You

Our business or commercial purposes for collecting, selling, or sharing that personal information

The categories of third parties with whom We share that personal information

The specific pieces of personal information We collected about You

If we sold or shared Your personal information for a business purpose, We will disclose to You:

The categories of personal information categories sold or disclosed and the categories of third parties to whom we have should or disclosed that information for a business purpose 

You have the right to make or obtain a transportable copy, no more than twice in twelve months, of Your Personal Information that we have collected in the period that is 12 months before the requested date and are maintaining. Make this Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com).. 

**The right to correct.** You have the right to correct inaccuracies in your personal data, taking into account the nature of the data and our purposes for processing it. 

**The right to opt-out to the sale of Personal Data.** You have the right to direct Us to not sell Your personal information. To submit an opt-out request please make this Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com).

**The right to opt-out of Cross-Context Behavioral Advertising.** You have the right to opt out of the sharing of your personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising as defined by the CPRA. To submit an opt-out Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com). Customers under 16 years must opt in to cross-context behavioral advertising. 

**The right to delete Personal Data.** You have the right to request the deletion of Your Personal Data, subject to certain exceptions. Once We receive and confirm Your request, We will delete (and direct Our Service Providers to delete) Your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies. We may deny Your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for Us or Our Service Providers to:

Complete the transaction for which We collected the personal information, provide a good or service that You requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with You, or otherwise perform our contract with You.

Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.

Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.

Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law.

Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 et. seq.).

Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, if You previously provided informed consent.

Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on Your relationship with Us.

Comply with a legal obligation.

Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which You provided it.

Make this Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com).

**The right not to be discriminated against.** You have the right not to be discriminated against for exercising any of Your consumer's rights. If you exercise your CCPA consumer rights: 

We will not deny goods or services to You

We will not charge different prices or rates for goods or services, including the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties

We will not provide a different level or quality of goods or services to You

We will not suggest that You will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services

We will not retaliate against You, as an employee, applicant for employment, or independent contractor 

We may still off you certain financial incentives permitted by the CCPA such as discounts, rewards, premium features, or loyalty accounts that can result in different prices, rates, or quality levels. 

**Exercising Your CCPA / CPRA Data Protection Rights**

In order to exercise any of Your rights under the CCPA / CPRA if You are a California resident, including to rights to know, access, or delete personal information, or opt out of the selling or sharing of your personal information, You, or an authorized agent, can contact Us:

By Privacy Request by clicking HERE 

By email: [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com)  

By phone number: 561-270-0650

Only You, or a person with lawful power of attorney that You authorize to act on Your behalf, may make a verifiable request related to Your personal information.

Your request to Us must:

Provide sufficient information that allows Us to reasonably verify You are the person about whom We collected personal information or an authorized representative

Describe Your request with sufficient detail that allows Us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it

We cannot respond to Your request or provide You with the required information if We cannot:

Verify Your identity or authority to make the request

And confirm that the personal information relates to You

We may ask for additional information from you, if we are unable to authenticate the request using commercially reasonable efforts, we may deny your request.  

We will disclose and deliver the required information free of charge within 45 days of receiving Your verifiable request. The time period to provide the required information may be extended once by an additional 45 days when reasonably necessary and with prior notice.

Any disclosures We provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding the verifiable request's receipt.

For data portability requests, We will select a format to provide Your personal information that is readily useable and should allow You to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.

Some information we collect about Consumers is not sufficiently associated with enough personal information for Us to be able to verify that it is a particular Consumer’s personal information. As required by the CCPA / CPRA, We do not include that personal information in response to Verifiable Consumer Requests. If We cannot comply with a request, We will explain the reasons in Our response. You may also have the right to appeal the denial of any of these rights by submitting an appeal Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com). 

**Do Not Sell My Personal Information**

You have the right to opt-out of the sale of Your personal information. Once We receive and confirm a verifiable consumer request from You, we will stop selling Your personal information. To exercise Your right to opt-out, please  make this Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com).

**"Do Not Track" Policy as Required by California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)**

Opt out Preference Signals. Your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit an opt-out preference signal, such as the Global Privacy Control (GPC) signal, to online services you visit. When we detect such signal, we place a U.S. Privacy String setting in your browser so that any third party who respects that signal will not track your activity on our Website. Your request to opt-out of sale/sharing will be linked to your browser identify only and not linked to any account information because the connection between your browser and the account is not known to us. GPC is supported by certain internet browsers or as a browser extension. You can find out how to enable GPC [here](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/). ([https://globalprivacycontrol.org](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/))  

**Nevada Privacy Rights**

Nevada residents may opt-out of the sale of certain "covered information" collected by operators of websites or online services under Nevada law.  Submit an opt-out Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com).

**Virginia Privacy Rights** 

This privacy notice section for Virginia residents under the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (VCDPA) and supplements the information contained in Our Privacy Policy and it applies solely to all visitors, users, and others who reside in the State of Virginia.

The terms used in this section have the same meaning as in the VCDPA. This section does not apply to information that is not considered “personal data”, such as deidentified or publicly available information as defined in the VCDPA. 

Virginia residents must give consent to Us, in a clear affirmative act signifying the Consumer’s freely given, specific, and informed and unambiguous agreement, before We process any of the Consumer’s personal information. 

**Categories of Personal Information Collected**

We may collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular Consumer. The following is a list of categories of personal information which we may collect or may have been collected from Virginia residents within the last twelve (12) months. Please refer to the **Purpose of Processing Personal Data, Transfer of Your Personal Data, and Disclosure of Your Personal Data** provisions for what categories of personal information is shared and why.

We may use de-identified data in some instances, as that is defined by the VCDPA. We will either maintain such data without attempting to re-identify it or treat such data as personal data subject to applicable law.

**Identifiers.**

Examples: A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, driver's license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.

**Personal information.**

Examples: A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver's license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories.

**Commercial information.**

Examples: Records and history of products or services purchased or considered.

**Internet or other similar network activity.**

Examples: Interaction with our Service or advertisement.

**VCDPA Sensitive Personal Data Considered Private that must be Protected Whether or Not Collected by Us**

Precise geolocation data - Collected: No.

Any information that reveals ethnic or racial origin - Collected: No.

Religious beliefs - Collected: No.

Sexual orientation - Collected: No.

Political Affiliations - Collected: No.

Mental or physical health diagnoses - Collected: No.

Immigration or citizenship standing - Collected: No.

Biometric data - Collected: No.

Personal information collected from a known minor under the age of 13 - Collected: No.

**Your Rights under the VCDPA** 

**The right to confirm if a Controller is processing your Personal Data and Access Personal Data:** Under VCDPA, You have the right to request that We disclose information to You about Our collection, use, sale, disclosure for business purposes, and share of personal information about You. You have the right to request access to your personal information in a portable format, and to correct inaccurate personal data or delete your personal 

Make this Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com).

**The right to correct:** You have the right to correct inaccuracies in your personal data, taking into account the nature of the data and our purposes for processing it. 

**The right to delete:** You have the right to request that We delete any personal data provided by or obtained about You. Subject to certain limitations, We will permanently delete any such personal data from our record and direct our processors to do the same. 

**The right to non-discrimination if you exercise your VCDPA consumer rights**:

We will not deny goods or services to you

We will not charge you different prices or rates for goods or services

We will not provide a different level or quality of goods or services to you

However, we may offer a different price, rate, level, quality, or selection of products or services if your personal data is required in order to provide those products or services and you have exercised your right to opt out, or the offer is related to a voluntary loyalty or rewards program.

**The right to opt out:** VCDPA provides Virginia residents with the right to 'opt out' of the processing of personal data for the following three purposes:

Targeted advertising;

Selling personal data; and

Profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning the consumer.

To opt out of the processing of personal data for the above purposes, please make this Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com).

Please note that the categories and examples provided in the list below are those defined in the VCDPA. This does not mean that all examples of that category of personal information were in fact processed by Us for any of the above purposes, but reflects our good faith belief to the best of our knowledge that some of that information from the applicable category may be and may have been collected for one of said purposes.

**Exercising Your VCDPA Privacy Rights**

In order to exercise any of Your rights under the VCDPA, and if You are a Virginia resident, You can contact Us:

By Privacy Request by clicking HERE

By email: [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com)  

By phone number: 561-270-0650

Your request to Us must:

Provide sufficient information that allows Us to reasonably verify You are the person about whom We collected personal information or an authorized representative

Describe Your request with sufficient detail that allows Us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it

We cannot respond to Your request or provide You with the required information if We cannot:

Verify Your identity or authority to make the request

And confirm that the personal information relates to You

We may ask for additional information from you, if we are unable to authenticate the request using commercially reasonable efforts, we may deny your request.  

We will disclose and deliver the required information free of charge within 45 days of receiving Your verifiable request. The time period to provide the required information may be extended once by an additional 45 days when reasonably necessary and with prior notice. 

Any disclosures We provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding the verifiable request's receipt.

For data portability requests, We will select a format to provide Your personal information that is readily useable and should allow You to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.

Some information we collect about Consumers is not sufficiently associated with enough personal information for Us to be able to verify that it is a particular Consumer’s personal information. As required by the VCDPA, We do not include that personal information in response to Verifiable Consumer Requests. If We cannot comply with a request, We will explain the reasons in Our response. You may also have the right to appeal the denial of any of these rights by submitting an appeal Privacy Request by clicking HERE or emailing us at [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com). 

If you believe that Your rights have been violated and you are not able to resolve the issue directly with us, you may file a complaint with the Virginia Attorney General’s Office.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. If You click on a third party link, You will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update Our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let You know via email and/or a prominent notice on Our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "Last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

**Notice of Financial Incentive**

Consumers who sign up for our marketing emails and/or SMS messages may receive a discount on their first purchase. A consumer provides their email address and/or phone number and consents to receive emails and SMS messages in exchange for a discount provided via promotion code. To opt in, a consumer must enter their email address or phone number into the form and submit it. A consumer may unsubscribe from our marketing emails by using the unsubscribe link in the email footer at any time. A consumer may unsubscribe from SMS messages by texting STOP to ### at any time. We calculate the value of the offer and financial incentive by using the expense related to the offer.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact us:

By email: [info@4ocean.com](mailto:info@4ocean.com)

By phone number: 561-270-0650

### Join the clean ocean movement

LEARN + ACT
-----------

SUPPORT
-------

JOIN THE CREW
-------------

WHOLESALE
---------

© Copyright 2024 4ocean Public Benefit Corp. All Rights Reserved

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.

 AED AFN ALL AMD ANG AUD AWG AZN BAM BBD BDT BGN BIF BOB BSD BWP BZD CAD CDF CHF CNY CRC CVE CZK DJF DKK DOP DZD EGP ETB EUR FJD FKP GBP GMD GNF GTQ GYD HKD HNL HUF IDR ILS INR ISK JMD JPY KES KGS KHR KMF KRW KYD KZT LAK LBP LKR MAD MDL MKD MMK MNT MOP MUR MVR MWK MYR NGN NIO NPR NZD PEN PGK PHP PKR PLN PYG QAR RON RSD RWF SAR SBD SEK SGD SHP SLL STD THB TJS TOP TTD TWD TZS UAH UGX USD UYU UZS VND VUV WST XAF XCD XOF XPF YER Submit
